Guide to the Editta Sherman Photographs 1940-1995 (bulk, undated) PR 322
New-York Historical Society
Editta Sherman photographs
1940-1995 (bulk, undated)
New-York Historical Society
Sherman, Editta
PR 322
14.5 Linear feet in seven flat boxes and two drawers
The collection includes approximately 700 portrait photographs taken by Editta Sherman (1912-2013). Sherman was a resident of the artist apartments above Carnegie Hall and is known for her portraits of celebrities. This collection includes primarily black and white photographs, and about fifteen color photographs. Subject individuals primarily include authors and other figures from literature, classical musicians, singers, actors, actresses, and other individuals connected to the performing arts, theatre, movies, and television. Figures from business, sports, art, and politics each make up a smaller portion of the collection.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials in this collection may be stored offsite. For more information on making arrangements to consult them, please visit www.nyhistory.org/library/visit.
Accruals
The collection also includes photographic negatives. As of February 2018, these have not yet been inventoried, but will be added to the finding aid in the future.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The collection was formed from donations made in July 2016 by members of Editta Sherman's family. Although the family members collaborated to form one overall donation, the donation of each photograph is attributable to a particular donor, based on the individual depicted in the photograph. Accordingly, the collection is organized to connect the Sherman donors with their related photographs.
Arrangement
The collection is organized in three series. Each series includes the photographs donated by particular Sherman family members:
Series I. The Kenneth Sherman Collection
Series II: The Melisande Sherman Collection
Series III: The Children of Lloyd Sherman Collection
Within each series, the photographs are arranged (and boxed) by size (8x10, 11x14, 16x20), with matted/other oversize photographs individually placed in oversize drawers. Within each box, the photographs are in alphabetical order by subject name. Images of a particular individual will be found in various boxes when that individual is represented with multiple size prints; the container list indicates these multiple locations.
About fifty of the photographs in the collection were included an exhibition at N-YHS in 2017. A slip of paper identifying a photograph as having been exhibited is included behind the photograph, within its enclosure. Exhibition items are also identified in the collections management system.
Biographical / Historical
Editta Sherman (1912-2013) was born in Philadelphia, the eldest child of Nunzio and Piernia Rinaolo, two recent Italian immigrants to the United States. Editta's father was a wedding and portrait photographer and she learned the trade from him during her youth. In 1935, she married Harold Sherman and would have five children with him. In the early years of their marriage, the Shermans lived in various places, including Martha's Vineyard where, in 1944, Editta opened a studio with her husband, who found the sitters and handled business matters.
In the mid-1940s, the Shermans moved to New York City. In 1949 they moved into one of the apartments above Carnegie Hall, taking up residence on the top floor in Studio 1208, which also served as Editta's photography studio. Formerly, the studio had been the center one of three apartments occupied by the sculptor Walter Russell. Although constantly worried about food and lodging, the Shermans were able to hold things together at the Carnegie Hall studio, though in the early 1950s they found a healthier environment out of the city for the children, with the hope of bringing the entire family back together when finances permitted. Harold died of diabetes in 1954, and Editta's work continued with an expanding celebrity clientele. Renowned as the "Duchess of Carnegie Hall," Sherman lived in Studio 1208 for 61 years until 2010 when, along with other residents, she was forced out by the Carnegie Hall Corporation, which sought to repurpose the apartments.
(The above note is based primarily on the New York Times obituary of 5 November 2013. Other sources include the Editta Sherman website and the introductory panel for the exhibition of Sherman's work held at N-YHS in 2017.)
Related Materials
Other collections at N-YHS relevant to Editta Sherman include:
Photographs from Editta Sherman's collaboration with fellow photographer and Carnegie Hall resident Bill Cunningham can be found in the Bill Cunningham Facades Photograph Collection (PR 307).
Photographs of Sherman and the Carnegie Hall apartments and residents can be found in the Melanie Tinnelly collection of photographs of or by Bill Cunningham and Toni "Suzette" Cimino (PR 329).
Scope and Contents
The collection includes approximately 700 portrait photographs taken by Editta Sherman. The bulk of the photographs are undated but range from the 1940s into the 1970s, with a few into the 1990s. The individuals depicted in the photographs are generally celebrity figures and are generally authors and other figures from literature, classical musicians, singers, actors, actresses, and playwrights and other individuals connected to the performing arts, theatre, movies, and television. Figures from business, sports, art, and politics make up a smaller portion of the collection. The container list includes reference to all individuals depicted in the photographs.
The bulk of the photographs are black and white. The few color photographs, about fifteen of them, are noted in the container list.
Some photographs were signed by Editta Sherman. These are noted in the container list. Many of the photographs have identifying references or other notations on the back.
Some photographs were inscribed to Sherman and/or autographed by their subject. These are noted in the container list.
Many, perhaps most, of the subjects are represented by multiple prints and poses. The container list indicates the approximate size of the prints, the number of prints, and the number of poses. Many of the prints are Gavelux.
Many of the photographs are in the original enclosures as received from the donor. Many of these enclosures include a label with a code assigned to the photo by family members. (In addition to appearing on the enclosures of the photographs, the codes were recorded by the processing archivist in the collections management system, but do not appear in the on-line finding aid. A version of the finding aid with the codes can be requested.)
Exhibitions
Following are the exhibitions, beginning in 2017 with N-YHS's exhibition of Editta Sherman photographs, in which selections from N-YHS's Editta Sherman collection were used.
The Duchess of Carnegie Hall: Photographs by Editta Sherman. Held at New-York Historical Society, 18 August to 15 October 2017.
Portrait photography; Celebrities.; Sherman, Editta
- Series I. The Kenneth Sherman Collection, 1942-1995 (bulk, undated); 4.83 Linear feet
  Immediate Source of Acquisition Note
  The photographs in this series were a gift in July 2016 of Kenneth Sherman, Editta Sherman's eldest son. (Credit line: Gift of Kenneth Sherman.)
  - 8 x 10 Photographs
    - Bryan Ahern (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Fay Bainter (3 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Rudolf Bing (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
      Scope and Contents Note
      Neither photograph explicitly identifies the subject as Bing. One of the photographs (used in the exhibition) is captioned on the reverse incorrectly as Louis Persinger.
    - Charles Boyer, Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Yul Brynner (7 photos/7 poses; one signed), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Pearl S. Buck (3 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - William F. Buckley (4 photos/4 poses/1 color), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Maurice Chevalier, 1975 (Offsite-box 1)
    - Norman Cousins (signed), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Joseph Cotton, Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Clara Damrosch (3 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Claude Dauphin (3 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Jimmy Dycks (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Nelson Eddy (3 photos/2 poses, one signed), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Maurice (or Charles?) Evans (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
      The photos are noted as "Maurice Evans" on the reverse, but the code assigned to them by the family indicates Charles (EvansC2320501 and 0601).
    - Alice Faye (3 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Malcolm Forbes (2 photos/1 pose), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Lillian Gish (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Vladimir Golschmann (7 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Gayelord Hauser (2 photos/1 pose), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Lillian Hellman, Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Walter Huston (3 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Aldous Huxley (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Efrem Kurtz (3 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Corliss Lamont (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Charles Laughton (9 photos/7 poses), 1965, Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Gertrude Lawrence (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Canada Lee (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Joshua Lieberman (4 photos/4 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - David Mannes (man with hand on chin) (2 photos/1 pose), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Marcel Marceau (5 photos/2 poses), 1977, Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Jackie Mason (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - David Merrick (3 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Sal Mineo (2 photos/1 pose), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Gene Nelson (4 photos/4 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Hugh O'Brian (4 photos/4 poses, 1 inscribed), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
      Includes photo of O'Brian as Wyatt Earp (inscribed).
    - Enzio Pinza (3 photos/2 poses, one inscribed), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Christopher Plummer (2 photos/one pose), 1955 (Offsite-box 1)
    - Franz Rupp (3 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Carl Sandburg (with guitar) (signed), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Carl Sandburg (10 photos/8 poses, one signed), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Don Shirley, Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Walter Slezak, 1955 (Offsite-box 1)
    - Leopold Stokowski (10 photos/7 poses, 4 signed), 1962, undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Carol Stone (3 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Norma Terris (3 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Walter Toscanini (3 photos/3 poses, 2 signed), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Amy Vanderbilt (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Felix Graf von Luckner (6 photos/4 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
    - Peggy Wood (2 photos/1 pose), Undated (Offsite-box 1)
  - 11 x 14 Photographs
    - Bryan Ahern (4 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Josef Astor (2 photos/one pose), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Charles Boyer (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Yul Brynner (5 photos/3 poses, 3 signed), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Oleg Cassini (5 photos/5 poses, 4 signed., Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Maurice Chevalier (3 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Joseph Cotton (3 photos/3 poses), 1967, Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Norman Cousins (2 photos/1 pose), 1945, Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Bob Crosby (4 photos/4 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Clara Damrosch (2 photos/one pose, one signed), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Claude Dauphin (7 photos/6 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Joe DiMaggio (3 photos/2 poses), 1952, 1955, Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Peter Duchin (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Nelson Eddy (4 photos/3 poses), 1952 (Offsite-box 4)
    - Maurice Evans (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Keith Funston (3 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - John K. Galbraith (7 photos/7 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - E. Franko Goldman (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Elliot Gould (5 photos/4 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Mike Gravel (7 photos/7 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Gayelord Hauser (5 photos/5 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Charlton Heston (3 photos/2 poses), 1945, Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Walter Huston, Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Aldous Huxley, Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Corliss Lamont [and family], Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Frances Langford (5 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Charles Laughton, Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Gertrude Lawrence (6 photos/6 poses, one signed), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Joshua Lieberman (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - David Mannes (3 photos/one pose, one inscribed), 1942, 1944, Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - David Merrick (2 photos/one pose), 1952 (Offsite-box 4)
    - Edward Mulhare (6 photos/6 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Lloyd Nolan (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Hugh O'Brian (5 photos/4 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Enzio Pinza (2 photos/one pose), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - [Enzio Pinza?] [man in profile], Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Buddy Rogers (5 photos/5 poses), 1952 (Offsite-box 4)
    - Carl Sandburg (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Cornelia Otis Skinner, Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Carol Stone, Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Leopold Stowkowski (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Norma Terris (4 photos/4 poses, one signed), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
    - Walter Toscanini (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 4)
  - 16 x 20 Photographs
    - Josef Astor, Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Yul Brynner, Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Pearl Buck, Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Maurice Chevalier, Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Claude Dauphin, Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Joe DiMaggio (signed), 1952 (Offsite-box 7)
    - Joe DiMaggio, Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Elliot Gould, Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Charlton Heston (signed), Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Aldous Huxley, Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - David Mannes (3 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Marcel Marceau (2 photos/one pose), Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Jackie Mason, Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Buddy Rodgers, Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Carl Sandburg, Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Carl Sandburg (color), Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Leopold Stokowski (3 photos/2 poses, one signed), Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Leopold Stokowski (signed), Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Earl Wild (3 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 7)
  - Matted & Other Oversize
    - Rudolph Bing (or Louis Persinger?), Undated (Drawer FF1)
      Persinger's name is written on the reverse, but the family coded the photo as Bing (BingR2070301).
    - Denise Darcel (color), Undated (Drawer FF1)
    - Malcolm Forbes (signed), Undated (Drawer FF1)
    - Lillian Gish (Drawer FF1)
    - E. Franko Goldman, Undated (Drawer FF1)
    - E. Franko Goldman, Undated (Drawer FF1)
    - E. Franko Goldman (signed), Undated (Drawer FF1)
    - Mike Gravel (color, signed), Undated (Drawer FF1)
    - Joel Grey, Undated (Drawer FF1)
    - Joel Grey (signed), Undated (Drawer FF1)
    - Corliss Lamont (color), Undated (Drawer FF1)
    - David Mannes, Undated (Drawer FF1)
    - Marcel Marceau (inscribed), 1995 (Drawer FF1)
    - Christopher Plummer (inscribed & signed), 1956 (Drawer FF1)
    - Leopold Stowkowski [Elderly man in blue shirt with document] (color), Undated (Drawer FF1)
    - Norma Terris (color), Undated (Drawer FF1)
- Series II. The Melisande Sherman Collection, 1940-1956 (bulk, undated); 4.83 Linear feet
  The photographs in this series were a gift of Melisande Sherman, Editta Sherman's daughter. (Credit line: Gift of Melisande Sherman.)
  - 8 x 10 Photographs
    - Barclay Acheson (4 photos/3 poses, one signed), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Robert Alda, Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Jean Pierre Aumont, Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Salvatore Baccaloni (2 photos/one pose)., Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Kaye Ballard, Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Richard Barr (5 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Mary Boland (4 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Shirley Booth (2 photos/one pose), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - David Brackman, Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Guido Cantelli (4 photos/2 poses), 1952, Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Jack Carter, Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Ilka Chase, Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Ruth Chatterton (2 photo/one pose), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Aaron Copland (color), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Katherine Cornell, Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Katherine Cornell [and Guthrie McClintic] (3 photos/one pose), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
      One signed and inscribed by Sherman to Christopher Plummer.
    - Hume Cronyn (3 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - John Daly (6 photos/6 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Howard Dietz (3 photos/one pose), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Antal Dorati, Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Max Eastman (3 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Richard Eastham (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Judith Evelyn (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Abel Ferrar (signed), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Paul Garrett, Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Barry Gray (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Cedric Hardwicke (2 photos/one pose), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Maurice Hindus (3 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - John Hodiak (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Judy Holliday (3 photos/2 poses), 1956, Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - John H. Holmes, Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Kim Hunter (4 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Richard Kiley (2 photos/one pose), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Charles LeMarie (4 photos/4 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Beatrice Lillie (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Hal March (4 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Candice March, Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Catherine Marshall (3 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Raymond Massey (3 photos/3 poses, one signed), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
      Includes signed photo of Massey as Abraham Lincoln
    - W.S. Maugham (2 photos/one pose, one signed), 1955, Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Guthrie McClintic (3 photos/one pose), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Ashley Montagu (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Anthony Norvell, Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Eugene Ormandy, Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Waldo Pierce (4 photos/4 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Tyrone Power and Others (10 photos/9 poses, some signed), 1953, Undated (Offsite-box 2)
      Includes photos of Power, Susan Kohner, Taryn Power, and another woman.
    - Thomas Schermer (signed), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Smallens, Alexander, Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Betty Smith (3 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - H. Allen Smith (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Jessica Tandy (4 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Bernard Waganaar (3 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Abraham Walkowitz (4 photos/3 poses, one signed), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
    - Oskar Werner (7 photos/3 poses, one signed), Undated (Offsite-box 2)
  - 11 x 14 Photographs
    - Barclay Acheson (Mrs.) (signed), 1945 (Offsite-box 5)
    - Eddy Albert (3 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Robert Alda, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Jean Pierre Aumont, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Salvatore Baccaloni (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - David Brackman, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Shirley Booth (5 photos/5 poses, one signed), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Jack Carter (3 photos/one pose), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Ilka Chase (5 photos/5 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Ruth Chatterton (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Aaron Copland, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Hume Cronyn, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Walter Damrosch, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Mario Del Monaco (3 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Howard Dietz (2 photos/one pose), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Antal Dorati / [Walter Damrosch] (signed), 1940, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
      Scope and Contents
      Includes 2 photos in the sleeve. One is of Dorati. The other is of an elderly man, which appears to be Walter Damrosch, and is signed and dated.
    - Eddie Dowling (signed), 1950 (Offsite-box 5)
    - Max Eastman (3 photos/3 poses, one signed), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Jinx Falkenberg (3 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - John Forsyth (4 photos/4 poses), 1954, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Joseph Fuchs (4 photos/4 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Paul Garrett, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Barry Gray (2 photos/2 poses, one signed), 1952, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Cedric Hardwicke, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - John Hodiak (4 photos/4 poses, one signed), 1952, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - John H. Holmes (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Hugo (Carnegie Hall painter) (signed), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Richard Kiley (4 photos/4 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Francis Lederer, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Beatrice Lillie (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Catherine Marshall (3 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Herbert Marshall (2 photos/one pose), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Raymond Massey (2 photos/2 poses), 1942, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - W. S. Maugham (4 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Elsa Maxwell (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Ashley Montagu (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Waldo Pierce, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Tyrone Power & Wife[?] (2 photos/2 poses, one signed), 1958, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Tyrone Power (5 photos/5 poses, one signed), 1955, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Basil Rathbone, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Thoughtful Ring Watch (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
      Individual in portrait is unidentified. "Thoughtful ring watch" is the description given on the original label.
    - Franco Rubatelli (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Betty Smith (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - H. Allen Smith (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Susan Strasberg (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Jessica Tandy and Hume Cronyn (3 photos/3 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Abraham Walkowitz, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Sam Wannamaker (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 5)
    - Efrem Zimbalist (3 photos/3 poses, 3 signed), 1942, 1946, Undated (Offsite-box 5)
  - 16 x 20 Photographs
    - Jean Pierre Aumont (signed), Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Dorothy Gish, Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Barry Gray, Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - John H. Holmes (2 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Francis Lederer, Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Hal March [and wife?] (2 photos/one pose), Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Elsa Maxwell, Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Tyrone Power (3 photos/2 poses), Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Basil Rathbone, Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Alexander Smallens, Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Betty Smith (color), Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - [Betty Smith] (color), Undated (Offsite-box 7)
    - Donald Wood, Undated (Offsite-box 7)
  - Matted & Other Oversize
    - Eddy Albert, Undated (Drawer FF2)
    - Aaron Copland (color), Undated (Drawer FF2)
    - Jeanne Dixon (color), Undated (Drawer FF2)
    - Walter Damrosch (signed), Undated (Drawer FF2)
    - Fahs [woman with brooch], Undated (Drawer FF2)
    - W. S. Maugham, Undated (Drawer FF2)